<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>synapsy on Blog | Peyronnet Group</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/tags/synapsy/</link><description>Recent content in synapsy on Blog | Peyronnet Group</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.peyronnet.group/tags/synapsy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Synapsy Write v2.5.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-250/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-250/</guid><description>A new version of Synapsy Write is now available and it is the version 2.5.0. This version adds several features, notably the new Synapsy Assistant Chat.
Synapsy Chat Assistant The new Chat feature of Synapsy Write revolutionizes document creation and information extraction by leveraging the advanced capabilities of GPT-3.5. This feature provides users with an interactive and intuitive UI to engage directly with an AI tailored for enhancing and drafting documents.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v2.4.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-240/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-240/</guid><description>A new version of Synapsy Write is now available and it is the version 2.4.0. This version adds several features such as the new editor mode or the new generations formats.
Manual Mode Previously, the sole method for crafting content via Synapsy was by employing AI-driven text generation. Presently, we&amp;rsquo;ve introduced the option to craft documents without relying on generative AI. Furthermore, our roadmap includes integrating a Copilot-style AI experience into the editor.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v2.3.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-230/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-230/</guid><description>Editor Synapsy Write introduces its innovative editor, empowering users with newfound control over their generated text. The latest update heralds a versatile array of features, including the ability to seamlessly edit saved generations. Users can now effortlessly customize titles, experiment with font styles, and explore various formatting options. While AI integration remains on the horizon, this editor lays a robust foundation for future advancements, promising a dynamic and personalized writing experience.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v2.2.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-220/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-220/</guid><description>In the ever-evolving landscape of technology, our commitment at Synapsy Write is to empower your creativity and streamline your document creation process. We are thrilled to introduce our new subscription plan
that promises unparalleled access to the limitless potential of Synapsy Write – the cutting-edge AI-powered document generation app.
Unlimited Access, Unmatched Value Starting at just €6 per month or €60 per year (with two months absolutely free), our subscription plan ensures that you have unrestricted access to the powerful features and capabilities of Synapsy Write.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v2.1.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-210/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-210/</guid><description>A new version of Synapsy Write is now available, and it brings the support for the Peyronnet Account. This means that you will now have to login to the app to use it.
Changelog New Added account system Added &amp;ldquo;New&amp;rdquo; label Updated Account is required to use the app Updated nav bar Updated dependencies Launch Click here
to launch the app.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Synapsy Write 2.0.0</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-200/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-200/</guid><description>The next major iteration of Synapsy Write is now available for everyone. This version introduces a new UI for mobile devices and new features. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive in!
Redesigned User Interface One of the most noticeable changes in the new UI is the new nav bar for mobile devices. The nav bar has two buttons: My Generations and Settings, with the Create button in the middle. The My Generations button allows you to access and manage all your previous and current generations.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v1.9.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-190/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-190/</guid><description>We are happy to introduce version 1.9.0 of Synapsy Write which brings the new text analysis (Philosophy) format. You can now ask a generative AI model to analyse an extract of a philosophic text to provide a clear understanding of it.
Changelog Added Added locales for text analysis Added text analysis options Added basic analysis format Added text analysis explanation format Added analysis outline format Added complex analysis format Fixed Improved margins on create page Updated Updated dependencies Launch Click here
to launch the app.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v1.8.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-180/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-180/</guid><description>A new version of Synapsy Write (v1.8) is now available! This version brings a new format generation mode: Tables. You can generates table easily using Synapsy Write by selecting the &amp;ldquo;Table&amp;rdquo; mode. We also improved several other areas of the app, like the format selector, and we added a new Generation Settings overview section which tells you the format, model and tone you chose.
Changelog Added Added table locales Added table prompts Added table styles Added table format Added new format dialog Added new format dialog selector Added new Generation Settings section Fixed Fixed an issue with table in dark theme Fixed wrong badge text Fixed tab index Updated Improved table styles on mobile Improved printing mode in Create page Updated version code Updated dependencies Launch Click here
to launch the app.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v1.7.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-170/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-170/</guid><description>A new version of Synapsy Write (v1.7) is now available and it brings the ability to remove an item from the generation history, but also the new tones feature. Indeed, it is now possible to specify a tone in which the response will be, such as professional, formal or funny.
Changelog Added Added date to generation item Added the possibility to remove an item from history Added tones locales Added new tone feature Fixed Fixed issues with import/export generations Updated Updated dependencies Launch Click here
to launch the app.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Synapsy Genidoc</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-synapsy-genidoc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 17:49:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-synapsy-genidoc/</guid><description>Why Synapsy Genidoc? Documentation is a crucial aspect of the software development process, yet it often falls by the wayside in the hustle and bustle of coding. With Synapsy Genidoc
, we aim to revolutionize the way developers approach documentation. This powerful Next.js application harnesses the capabilities of OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s GPT models to simplify and expedite the documentation creation process.
Streamlining Documentation Creation Traditionally, writing documentation involves the tedious task of manually crafting Markdown files to explain code functionality.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v1.6.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-160/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-160/</guid><description>A new version of Synapsy Write (v1.6) is now available and it brings variables. Variables are a new way to input data to Synapsy, making it more efficient to provide additional context for your generation.
Changelog Added Added variable interface Added new variable locales Added variable item component Added variable system Added variables to prompts Fixed Fixed an issue with empty history Updated Updated dependencies Launch Click here
to launch the app.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v1.5.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-150/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-150/</guid><description>A new version of Synapsy Write (v1.5) is now available and it removes loading screens. You can now see the model generation directly, just like on ChatGPT.
Changelog Added Added streaming feature for basic generation Added cursor Improved experience for streamed response Added streamed response for complex generations Formatting is now happening in real time Fixed Fixed a type issue Updated Updated dependencies Launch Click here
to launch the app.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v1.4.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-140/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-140/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that Synapsy Write v1.4 is now available. This version brings new options when generating content, so you have more control over the output of the model.
Changelog New Added slider component Added hover card component Added locales for advanced options Added temperature option Added Top P option Added frequency penalty Added presence penalty option Added OpenAiOptions interface Added advanced options Updated Updated dependencies Launch Click here
to launch the app.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v1.3.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-130/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that Synapsy Write v1.3 is now available. This version brings UI improvements and fixes.
Note: This changelog also includes changes made in hotfixes (1.3.1, 1.3.2 and 1.3.3)
Changelog New Add new button styles Create button is now disabled if no prompt is given Improved code for View page Added locales for View page Improved layout Added scale effect Added formats selector locales Added new formats selector Fixed Fixed Learn More button Fixed space issue with navbar Fixed display issue on mobile devices Updated Improved landing page Updated footer Updated next config Updated model list Improved outline prompts Updated dependencies Launch Click here
to launch the app.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v1.2.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-120/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-120/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that Synapsy Write v1.2 is now available with several new features and improvements.
Changelog New Added the possibility to edit API Key Added export and import buttons Added locales Added error messages Added footer Added home page content Fixed Fixed an issue with API Key panel Fixed scrolling issue (#2) Launch Click here
to launch the app.
We hope you enjoy using Synapsy Write v1.2 and we look forward to hearing your feedback.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v1.1.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-110/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-110/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that Synapsy Write v1.1 is now available with several new features and improvements.
Changelog New Switched to URL params Added new philosophy options (essay basic and complex) Improved the look of results Added the possibility to select the model Added stats section Added print and copy button Fixed Fixed an issue with item card in history Launch Click here
to launch the app.</description></item></channel></rss>