<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>information on Blog | Peyronnet Group</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/tags/information/</link><description>Recent content in information on Blog | Peyronnet Group</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 17:49:22 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.peyronnet.group/tags/information/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introducing Synapsy Genidoc</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-synapsy-genidoc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 17:49:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-synapsy-genidoc/</guid><description>Why Synapsy Genidoc? Documentation is a crucial aspect of the software development process, yet it often falls by the wayside in the hustle and bustle of coding. With Synapsy Genidoc
, we aim to revolutionize the way developers approach documentation. This powerful Next.js application harnesses the capabilities of OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s GPT models to simplify and expedite the documentation creation process.
Streamlining Documentation Creation Traditionally, writing documentation involves the tedious task of manually crafting Markdown files to explain code functionality.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Synapsy</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-synapsy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 15:54:33 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-synapsy/</guid><description>Introduction Synapsy is a subdivision of Peyronnet Group focused on creating and delivering AI experiences and projects that aim to enhance human capabilities by improving productivity. Synapsy has already released its first app: Synapsy Write.
Synapsy Write Synapsy Write is a Next.js web application that runs on any browser and device. It allows users to choose from different types of text content, such as website paragraphs, blog posts, essays, and more.</description></item><item><title>Communication Strategy Update</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/communication-strategy-update/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 14:05:08 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/communication-strategy-update/</guid><description>Update on the communication strategy for Léo Corporation and Devyus on YouTube Hello everyone,
We have some exciting news to share with you regarding our communication strategy for Léo Corporation and Devyus on YouTube. As you may have noticed, the Léo Corporation YouTube channel has been closed and will be moved to the Peyronnet Group&amp;rsquo;s YouTube channel. This is part of our plan to consolidate our online presence and create a unified brand identity for our group.</description></item><item><title>Devyus is introducing XValid</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-xvalid/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 11:37:55 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-xvalid/</guid><description>🎉 XValid - First Release 🎉 We are thrilled to announce the first release of XValid - a simple C# validator library that makes it easy to validate various types of data. Whether you need to validate email addresses, ISBNs, IBANs, credit card numbers, IP addresses, or geographic coordinates, XValid has got you covered!
What is XValid? XValid is a lightweight and versatile library designed to help developers implement data validation effortlessly.</description></item><item><title>Peyronnet Group's Subsidiary, Léo Corporation, Sets New Records with a Productive July</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/productive-month-leo-corporation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 16:29:49 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/productive-month-leo-corporation/</guid><description>Léo Corporation, a subsidiary of Peyronnet Group, has had an exceptionally productive month in July, with a flurry of new product launches and updates that have left customers delighted and impressed. The company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to innovation and delivering user-friendly solutions is evident in the array of tools and utilities it introduced to the market. Let&amp;rsquo;s take a closer look at the exciting products and updates that have been rolled out:</description></item><item><title>Safely Downloading Peyronnet Group Apps and Software: Trusted Sources and Misconceptions</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/software-distribution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/software-distribution/</guid><description>Introduction Peyronnet Group is dedicated to delivering high-quality web apps and Windows applications to its users. As a responsible software provider, the company takes utmost care to ensure the safety and security of its products during distribution. In this article, we will explore the trusted sources from which you can safely download Peyronnet Group (including Léo Corporation and Devyus) apps and address some common misconceptions surrounding the safety of their software.</description></item><item><title>Introducing The Peyronnet Group</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-peyronnet-group/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 09:18:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-peyronnet-group/</guid><description>Hello everyone, we are the Peyronnet Group - a newly formed organization that brings together two innovative companies in the tech industry: Léo Corporation and Devyus. We are excited to introduce ourselves to you and share our vision for the future.
Léo Corporation, founded in 2017 by Léo Peyronnet, specializes in developing mobile applications and software solutions. Our focus is on creating innovative and user-friendly applications that make life easier and more enjoyable for our users.</description></item></channel></rss>