<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Blog | Peyronnet Group</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Blog | Peyronnet Group</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Synapsy Write v2.7.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-270/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-270/</guid><description>A new version of Synapsy Write is now available and it is the version 2.7.0. This version includes new oral presentation formats, new system prompts customization, and more!
Oral presentation format Synapsy Write has introduced a groundbreaking feature with its new oral presentation formats, designed specifically to assist users in preparing for effective and engaging spoken presentations. This addition offers tailored templates and structures that simplify the process of organizing and delivering information verbally.</description></item><item><title>Stat report for Léo Corporation and Devyus in May 2024</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-may-2024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-may-2024/</guid><description>The stat report for May 2024 is now available.
Léo Corporation The Evolution of Léo Corporation&amp;rsquo;s App Downloads in May 2024 Léo Corporation, known for its innovative and user-friendly software solutions, has witnessed substantial growth in the number of downloads for its apps over the past few months. May 2024 was particularly significant, with several of the corporation’s apps experiencing notable increases in their download counts. This blog post will delve into the detailed evolution of these downloads, highlighting key trends and insights.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v2.6.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-260/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-260/</guid><description>A new version of Synapsy Write is now available and it is the version 2.6.0. We added Conversation Management, new formats, and made several improvements to the app
History paragraph format The new History paragraph format in Synapsy Write is designed to generate high-quality historical content with precision and clarity. Leveraging a specialized method tailored for history subjects, the AI begins each paragraph with a general statement of the main idea.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v2.5.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-250/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-250/</guid><description>A new version of Synapsy Write is now available and it is the version 2.5.0. This version adds several features, notably the new Synapsy Assistant Chat.
Synapsy Chat Assistant The new Chat feature of Synapsy Write revolutionizes document creation and information extraction by leveraging the advanced capabilities of GPT-3.5. This feature provides users with an interactive and intuitive UI to engage directly with an AI tailored for enhancing and drafting documents.</description></item><item><title>Stat report for Léo Corporation and Devyus in April 2024</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-april-2024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-april-2024/</guid><description>Léo Corporation April 2024 witnessed continued growth and engagement across Léo Corporation&amp;rsquo;s diverse range of applications. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the download evolution for each software:
App Performance Overview Gavilya: Steady Expansion Gavilya maintained its upward trajectory, with a notable increase of 222 downloads in April. This consistent growth reflects Gavilya&amp;rsquo;s enduring popularity and effectiveness in providing users with intuitive and feature-rich solutions.
InternetTest Pro 8: Remarkable Surge InternetTest Pro 8 experienced a significant surge in April, with an impressive increase of 1,598 downloads.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v2.4.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-240/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-240/</guid><description>A new version of Synapsy Write is now available and it is the version 2.4.0. This version adds several features such as the new editor mode or the new generations formats.
Manual Mode Previously, the sole method for crafting content via Synapsy was by employing AI-driven text generation. Presently, we&amp;rsquo;ve introduced the option to craft documents without relying on generative AI. Furthermore, our roadmap includes integrating a Copilot-style AI experience into the editor.</description></item><item><title>Stat report for Léo Corporation and Devyus in February 2024</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-february-2024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-february-2024/</guid><description>Léo Corporation February 2024 witnessed another month of steady growth for Léo Corporation&amp;rsquo;s suite of apps, with significant increases recorded across various offerings. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the details of this month&amp;rsquo;s download evolution.
App Performance Overview Gavilya: Maintaining Momentum Gavilya, Léo Corporation&amp;rsquo;s flagship app, continued its consistent performance, adding 144 downloads in February. While this represents a slight decrease in growth rate compared to the previous month, Gavilya remains a cornerstone of the corporation&amp;rsquo;s offerings.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v2.3.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-230/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-230/</guid><description>Editor Synapsy Write introduces its innovative editor, empowering users with newfound control over their generated text. The latest update heralds a versatile array of features, including the ability to seamlessly edit saved generations. Users can now effortlessly customize titles, experiment with font styles, and explore various formatting options. While AI integration remains on the horizon, this editor lays a robust foundation for future advancements, promising a dynamic and personalized writing experience.</description></item><item><title>Stat report for Léo Corporation and Devyus in January 2024</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-january-2024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-january-2024/</guid><description>Léo Corporation As we step into the new year, the download numbers for Léo Corporation&amp;rsquo;s apps in January 2024 reveal an impressive surge, setting a promising tone for the months ahead. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the data and unravel the story behind the numbers.
Apps Gavilya - A Continuing Ascend Gavilya, the flagship app of Léo Corporation, maintained its upward trajectory with 166 additional downloads in January. This marks a 6.24% increase from the previous month, showcasing a steady and consistent rise in user engagement.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v2.2.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-220/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-220/</guid><description>In the ever-evolving landscape of technology, our commitment at Synapsy Write is to empower your creativity and streamline your document creation process. We are thrilled to introduce our new subscription plan
that promises unparalleled access to the limitless potential of Synapsy Write – the cutting-edge AI-powered document generation app.
Unlimited Access, Unmatched Value Starting at just €6 per month or €60 per year (with two months absolutely free), our subscription plan ensures that you have unrestricted access to the powerful features and capabilities of Synapsy Write.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v2.1.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-210/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-210/</guid><description>A new version of Synapsy Write is now available, and it brings the support for the Peyronnet Account. This means that you will now have to login to the app to use it.
Changelog New Added account system Added &amp;ldquo;New&amp;rdquo; label Updated Account is required to use the app Updated nav bar Updated dependencies Launch Click here
to launch the app.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the Peyronnet Account</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-account/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-account/</guid><description>Introduction At Peyronnet Group, we understand the importance of a unified digital experience. The Peyronnet Account is designed to bring together various facets of your online life, creating a cohesive environment that simplifies and enhances your interactions with the digital world.
One of the key highlights of the Peyronnet Account is its seamless integration with Synapsy Write. Say goodbye to the hassle of managing multiple accounts and passwords. With your Peyronnet Account, you can effortlessly connect to Synapsy Write and experience a new level of convenience.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Synapsy Write 2.0.0</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-200/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-200/</guid><description>The next major iteration of Synapsy Write is now available for everyone. This version introduces a new UI for mobile devices and new features. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive in!
Redesigned User Interface One of the most noticeable changes in the new UI is the new nav bar for mobile devices. The nav bar has two buttons: My Generations and Settings, with the Create button in the middle. The My Generations button allows you to access and manage all your previous and current generations.</description></item><item><title>Stat report for Léo Corporation and Devyus in December 2023</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-december-2023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-december-2023/</guid><description>As we bid farewell to 2023, we embark on a final exploration of the download statistics for Léo Corporation&amp;rsquo;s apps and Devyus&amp;rsquo; products. This journey through December&amp;rsquo;s data offers a conclusive look at how user engagement and preferences evolved over the course of the year.
Léo Corporation December App Performance Analysis Gavilya - Closing the Year with Triumph Gavilya concluded the year on a triumphant note, adding 159 downloads in December.</description></item><item><title>Communication Strategy on TikTok Update</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/communication-strategy-update-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/communication-strategy-update-2/</guid><description>We have some exciting news to share with you! As you may know, Léo Corporation has recently been integrated with Peyronnet Group, a leading company in the fields of innovation, technology and more. This means that we can now offer you a wider range of products and services that will help you achieve your goals and dreams.
To reflect this change, we have decided to rebrand our TikTok account from @leocorporation_ to @peyronnetgroup.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v1.9.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-190/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-190/</guid><description>We are happy to introduce version 1.9.0 of Synapsy Write which brings the new text analysis (Philosophy) format. You can now ask a generative AI model to analyse an extract of a philosophic text to provide a clear understanding of it.
Changelog Added Added locales for text analysis Added text analysis options Added basic analysis format Added text analysis explanation format Added analysis outline format Added complex analysis format Fixed Improved margins on create page Updated Updated dependencies Launch Click here
to launch the app.</description></item><item><title>PeyrSharp: Version 2.1.0.2312 is now available</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-2102312/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-2102312/</guid><description>Version 2.1.0.2312 of PeyrSharp is now available. This version brings new features for the Converter module and more.
Changelog PeyrSharp.Core New Added DownloadFile() method (#157) Added XML Documentation Added new overload for GenerateAsync() in Password (#158) Added CelsiusToKelvin() method (#159) Added FahrenheitToKelvin() method (#159) Added KelvinToCelsius() method (#159) Added KelvinToFahrenheit() method (#159) NuGet Packages PeyrSharp
PeyrSharp.Core
PeyrSharp.Enums
PeyrSharp.Env
PeyrSharp.Exceptions
PeyrSharp.Extensions
PeyrSharp.UiHelpers
Links Documentation
GitHub
GitHub Packages</description></item><item><title>Stat report for Léo Corporation and Devyus in November 2023</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-november-2023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 16:43:06 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-november-2023/</guid><description>As the year draws to a close, we embark on a journey through the download statistics of Léo Corporation&amp;rsquo;s apps and Devyus&amp;rsquo; Products for the month of November 2023.
Léo Corporation This analysis provides a comprehensive overview of the evolving trends, user preferences, and the performance of various applications within Léo Corporation&amp;rsquo;s diverse software portfolio.
While the previous months have seen consistent growth and adaptations in download figures, November offers a fresh perspective on how these applications are resonating with users.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v1.8.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-180/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-180/</guid><description>A new version of Synapsy Write (v1.8) is now available! This version brings a new format generation mode: Tables. You can generates table easily using Synapsy Write by selecting the &amp;ldquo;Table&amp;rdquo; mode. We also improved several other areas of the app, like the format selector, and we added a new Generation Settings overview section which tells you the format, model and tone you chose.
Changelog Added Added table locales Added table prompts Added table styles Added table format Added new format dialog Added new format dialog selector Added new Generation Settings section Fixed Fixed an issue with table in dark theme Fixed wrong badge text Fixed tab index Updated Improved table styles on mobile Improved printing mode in Create page Updated version code Updated dependencies Launch Click here
to launch the app.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v1.7.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-170/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-170/</guid><description>A new version of Synapsy Write (v1.7) is now available and it brings the ability to remove an item from the generation history, but also the new tones feature. Indeed, it is now possible to specify a tone in which the response will be, such as professional, formal or funny.
Changelog Added Added date to generation item Added the possibility to remove an item from history Added tones locales Added new tone feature Fixed Fixed issues with import/export generations Updated Updated dependencies Launch Click here
to launch the app.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Synapsy Genidoc</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-synapsy-genidoc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 17:49:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-synapsy-genidoc/</guid><description>Why Synapsy Genidoc? Documentation is a crucial aspect of the software development process, yet it often falls by the wayside in the hustle and bustle of coding. With Synapsy Genidoc
, we aim to revolutionize the way developers approach documentation. This powerful Next.js application harnesses the capabilities of OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s GPT models to simplify and expedite the documentation creation process.
Streamlining Documentation Creation Traditionally, writing documentation involves the tedious task of manually crafting Markdown files to explain code functionality.</description></item><item><title>PeyrSharp: Version 2.0.0.2311 is now available</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-2002311/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 13:36:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-2002311/</guid><description>Version 2.0.0.2311 of PeyrSharp is now available. This version doesn&amp;rsquo;t bring any new features; however, we added .NET 8 to the list of targeted frameworks. Please also note that we decided to remove support for .NET 5 since it is no longer supported. If you still rely on .NET 5, we advise you to upgrade to .NET 6 or 8 for Long Term Support (LTS).
NuGet Packages PeyrSharp
PeyrSharp.Core
PeyrSharp.Enums
PeyrSharp.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v1.6.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-160/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-160/</guid><description>A new version of Synapsy Write (v1.6) is now available and it brings variables. Variables are a new way to input data to Synapsy, making it more efficient to provide additional context for your generation.
Changelog Added Added variable interface Added new variable locales Added variable item component Added variable system Added variables to prompts Fixed Fixed an issue with empty history Updated Updated dependencies Launch Click here
to launch the app.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v1.5.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-150/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-150/</guid><description>A new version of Synapsy Write (v1.5) is now available and it removes loading screens. You can now see the model generation directly, just like on ChatGPT.
Changelog Added Added streaming feature for basic generation Added cursor Improved experience for streamed response Added streamed response for complex generations Formatting is now happening in real time Fixed Fixed a type issue Updated Updated dependencies Launch Click here
to launch the app.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v1.4.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-140/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-140/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that Synapsy Write v1.4 is now available. This version brings new options when generating content, so you have more control over the output of the model.
Changelog New Added slider component Added hover card component Added locales for advanced options Added temperature option Added Top P option Added frequency penalty Added presence penalty option Added OpenAiOptions interface Added advanced options Updated Updated dependencies Launch Click here
to launch the app.</description></item><item><title>Evolution of downloads in October 2023</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-october-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 10:13:06 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-october-2023/</guid><description>As the leaves change and autumn sweeps in, it&amp;rsquo;s time to take a fresh look at the download statistics for Léo Corporation&amp;rsquo;s apps in October 2023.
Léo Corporation Understanding the Data Before we dive into the October numbers, let&amp;rsquo;s briefly recap the software applications under consideration:
Gavilya InternetTest Pro 7 Datalya ColorPicker Max 5 DayBar PermaTop The provided data includes download figures for each of these applications from January to September 2023, along with the September and October figures.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v1.3.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-130/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that Synapsy Write v1.3 is now available. This version brings UI improvements and fixes.
Note: This changelog also includes changes made in hotfixes (1.3.1, 1.3.2 and 1.3.3)
Changelog New Add new button styles Create button is now disabled if no prompt is given Improved code for View page Added locales for View page Improved layout Added scale effect Added formats selector locales Added new formats selector Fixed Fixed Learn More button Fixed space issue with navbar Fixed display issue on mobile devices Updated Improved landing page Updated footer Updated next config Updated model list Improved outline prompts Updated dependencies Launch Click here
to launch the app.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v1.2.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-120/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-120/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that Synapsy Write v1.2 is now available with several new features and improvements.
Changelog New Added the possibility to edit API Key Added export and import buttons Added locales Added error messages Added footer Added home page content Fixed Fixed an issue with API Key panel Fixed scrolling issue (#2) Launch Click here
to launch the app.
We hope you enjoy using Synapsy Write v1.2 and we look forward to hearing your feedback.</description></item><item><title>Synapsy Write v1.1.0 Changelog</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-110/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/synsapsy-write-version-110/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that Synapsy Write v1.1 is now available with several new features and improvements.
Changelog New Switched to URL params Added new philosophy options (essay basic and complex) Improved the look of results Added the possibility to select the model Added stats section Added print and copy button Fixed Fixed an issue with item card in history Launch Click here
to launch the app.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Synapsy</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-synapsy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 15:54:33 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-synapsy/</guid><description>Introduction Synapsy is a subdivision of Peyronnet Group focused on creating and delivering AI experiences and projects that aim to enhance human capabilities by improving productivity. Synapsy has already released its first app: Synapsy Write.
Synapsy Write Synapsy Write is a Next.js web application that runs on any browser and device. It allows users to choose from different types of text content, such as website paragraphs, blog posts, essays, and more.</description></item><item><title>Evolution of downloads in September 2023</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-september-2023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 09:52:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-september-2023/</guid><description>In the fast-paced world of technology, where innovation and evolution are constants, the performance and adoption of software applications and developer tools play a pivotal role in shaping the landscape. In this blog post, we embark on a journey to explore the dynamics of Léo Corporation and Devyus.
Léo Corporation Léo Corporation has a diverse portfolio of applications, each catering to different user needs. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a closer look at the evolution of the number of downloads of Léo Corporation&amp;rsquo;s apps for the month of September 2023.</description></item><item><title>PeyrSharp: Version 1.10.0.2310 is now available</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-11002310/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 15:37:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-11002310/</guid><description>Version 1.10.0.2310 of PeyrSharp is now available, let&amp;rsquo;s see what&amp;rsquo;s new.
Changelog PeyrSharp.UiHelpers New Added the possibility to close windows (#143) Added the possibility to maximize windows (#143) Added the possibility to restore windows (#143) Added the possibility to minimize windows (#143) Added XML documentation (#143) Added the possibility to set the position of any window (#144) Added SetTopMost() method (#145) Added GetWindowSize() method (#146) Fixed Fixed an issue with wrong method NuGet Packages PeyrSharp
PeyrSharp.</description></item><item><title>Evolving Excellence: Léo Corporation and Devyus' Downloads in August</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-august-2023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 21:15:15 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-august-2023/</guid><description>Léo Corporation Introduction As the tech world advanced into August 2023, Léo Corporation continued its trailblazing journey in the realm of app development. This article charts the trajectory of Léo Corporation&amp;rsquo;s app downloads during this pivotal month, shedding light on their commitment to innovation and user satisfaction. Amidst the data, a clear narrative emerges — one of growth, evolution, and the relentless pursuit of excellence.
Gavilya and InternetTest Pro 7 Gavilya, a stalwart in Léo Corporation&amp;rsquo;s app lineup, garnered 2,077 downloads in August, showcasing a steadfast 3.</description></item><item><title>PeyrSharp: Version 1.9.0.2309 is now available</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-1902309/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 11:14:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-1902309/</guid><description>Version 1.9.0.2309 of PeyrSharp is now available, let&amp;rsquo;s see what&amp;rsquo;s new.
Changelog PeyrSharp.Core PeyrSharp.Env New Added LaunchUWPApp(UwpApp) (#137) Added CurrentTheme property (#138) PeyrSharp.Extensions New Added ToLowerAt(s) (#136) Added ToLowerAt(str, r) (#136) PeyrSharp.UiHelpers New Added WindowInfo class (#139) Added the possibility to get a list of opened windows (#139) NuGet Packages PeyrSharp
PeyrSharp.Core
PeyrSharp.Enums
PeyrSharp.Env
PeyrSharp.Exceptions
PeyrSharp.Extensions
PeyrSharp.UiHelpers
Links Documentation
GitHub
GitHub Packages</description></item><item><title>Communication Strategy Update</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/communication-strategy-update/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 14:05:08 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/communication-strategy-update/</guid><description>Update on the communication strategy for Léo Corporation and Devyus on YouTube Hello everyone,
We have some exciting news to share with you regarding our communication strategy for Léo Corporation and Devyus on YouTube. As you may have noticed, the Léo Corporation YouTube channel has been closed and will be moved to the Peyronnet Group&amp;rsquo;s YouTube channel. This is part of our plan to consolidate our online presence and create a unified brand identity for our group.</description></item><item><title>Stat Report on Léo Corporation and Devyus: July 2023 Edition</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-july-2023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 20:53:54 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-july-2023/</guid><description>Introduction In the ever-evolving world of software development, two prominent entities have been making waves with their innovative and user-centric offerings. Léo Corporation and Devyus, both subsidiaries of the esteemed Peyronnet Group, have consistently demonstrated their commitment to excellence and customer satisfaction. In the spotlight of this blog post, we unravel the captivating stories of their apps and NuGet packages, respectively, and explore the remarkable growth they experienced in July 2023.</description></item><item><title>PeyrSharp: Version 1.8.0.2308 is now available</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-1802308/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 11:10:31 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-1802308/</guid><description>Version 1.8.0.2308 of PeyrSharp is now available, let&amp;rsquo;s see what&amp;rsquo;s new.
Changelog PeyrSharp.Core New Added Save() method in XmlHelper (#126) Added Load() method in XmlHelper (#127) Added Save() method in JsonHelper (#128) Added Load() method in JsonHelper (#129) NuGet Packages PeyrSharp
PeyrSharp.Core
PeyrSharp.Enums
PeyrSharp.Env
PeyrSharp.Exceptions
PeyrSharp.Extensions
PeyrSharp.UiHelpers
Links Documentation
GitHub
GitHub Packages</description></item><item><title>Devyus is introducing XValid</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-xvalid/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 11:37:55 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-xvalid/</guid><description>🎉 XValid - First Release 🎉 We are thrilled to announce the first release of XValid - a simple C# validator library that makes it easy to validate various types of data. Whether you need to validate email addresses, ISBNs, IBANs, credit card numbers, IP addresses, or geographic coordinates, XValid has got you covered!
What is XValid? XValid is a lightweight and versatile library designed to help developers implement data validation effortlessly.</description></item><item><title>Peyronnet Group's Subsidiary, Léo Corporation, Sets New Records with a Productive July</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/productive-month-leo-corporation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 16:29:49 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/productive-month-leo-corporation/</guid><description>Léo Corporation, a subsidiary of Peyronnet Group, has had an exceptionally productive month in July, with a flurry of new product launches and updates that have left customers delighted and impressed. The company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to innovation and delivering user-friendly solutions is evident in the array of tools and utilities it introduced to the market. Let&amp;rsquo;s take a closer look at the exciting products and updates that have been rolled out:</description></item><item><title>Safely Downloading Peyronnet Group Apps and Software: Trusted Sources and Misconceptions</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/software-distribution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/software-distribution/</guid><description>Introduction Peyronnet Group is dedicated to delivering high-quality web apps and Windows applications to its users. As a responsible software provider, the company takes utmost care to ensure the safety and security of its products during distribution. In this article, we will explore the trusted sources from which you can safely download Peyronnet Group (including Léo Corporation and Devyus) apps and address some common misconceptions surrounding the safety of their software.</description></item><item><title>The Surging Success of Léo Corporation's Apps and Devyus products: June 2023 Download Evolution</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-june-2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 10:39:20 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-june-2023/</guid><description>Introduction In the dynamic world of software development, companies strive to create innovative solutions that meet the evolving needs of users and developers alike. Two prominent entities making waves in this realm are Léo Corporation and Devyus, both subsidiaries of the Peyronnet Group. Léo Corporation is renowned for its user-friendly and feature-rich apps, while Devyus specializes in providing cutting-edge NuGet packages for developers. As we delve into the data for June 2023, it becomes clear that both Léo Corporation and Devyus have experienced impressive growth in terms of downloads, showcasing their commitment to excellence and the value they bring to their respective industries.</description></item><item><title>PeyrSharp: Version 1.7.0.2307 is now available</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-1702307/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-1702307/</guid><description>Version 1.7.0.2307 of PeyrSharp is now available, let&amp;rsquo;s see what&amp;rsquo;s new.
Changelog PeyrSharp.Core New Added Range() method in Stats (#117) Added Variance() method in Stats (#118) Added StandardDeviation() method in Stats (#119) Updated Improved exceptions PeyrSharp.Env New Added UwpApp record (#120) Added the possibility to get UWP apps asynchronously (#120) NuGet Packages PeyrSharp
PeyrSharp.Core
PeyrSharp.Enums
PeyrSharp.Env
PeyrSharp.Exceptions
PeyrSharp.Extensions
PeyrSharp.UiHelpers
Links Documentation
GitHub
GitHub Packages</description></item><item><title>PeyrSharp: Version 1.6.0.2305 is now available</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-1602305/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 10:44:43 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-1602305/</guid><description>Version 1.6.0.2305 of PeyrSharp is now available, let&amp;rsquo;s see what&amp;rsquo;s new.
Changelog PeyrSharp.Core New Added a method to convert bits to bytes (#100) Added a method to convert bytes to bits (#101) Added a method to convert mach to km/h (#102) Added a method to convert mach to miles/h (#103) Added a StatusInfo class (#104) Added a method that gets the status info of a URL (#105) NuGet Packages PeyrSharp
PeyrSharp.</description></item><item><title>Introducing The Peyronnet Group</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-peyronnet-group/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 09:18:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-peyronnet-group/</guid><description>Hello everyone, we are the Peyronnet Group - a newly formed organization that brings together two innovative companies in the tech industry: Léo Corporation and Devyus. We are excited to introduce ourselves to you and share our vision for the future.
Léo Corporation, founded in 2017 by Léo Peyronnet, specializes in developing mobile applications and software solutions. Our focus is on creating innovative and user-friendly applications that make life easier and more enjoyable for our users.</description></item><item><title>Léo Corporation and Devyus See Impressive Growth in April 2023.</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-april-2023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 09:18:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-april-2023/</guid><description>Introduction In the world of software development, it&amp;rsquo;s not easy to stand out from the crowd. However, Peyronnet Group&amp;rsquo;s subsidiaries, Léo Corporation and Devyus, have managed to do just that. In April 2023, both companies saw impressive growth in their respective areas of expertise.
Léo Corporation First, let&amp;rsquo;s take a closer look at Léo Corporation. This innovative company is known for developing cutting-edge software applications that help users in various areas of their lives.</description></item></channel></rss>