<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Blog | Peyronnet Group</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Blog | Peyronnet Group</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 11:10:31 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PeyrSharp: Version 1.8.0.2308 is now available</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-1802308/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 11:10:31 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-1802308/</guid><description>Version 1.8.0.2308 of PeyrSharp is now available, let&amp;rsquo;s see what&amp;rsquo;s new.
Changelog PeyrSharp.Core New Added Save() method in XmlHelper (#126) Added Load() method in XmlHelper (#127) Added Save() method in JsonHelper (#128) Added Load() method in JsonHelper (#129) NuGet Packages PeyrSharp
PeyrSharp.Core
PeyrSharp.Enums
PeyrSharp.Env
PeyrSharp.Exceptions
PeyrSharp.Extensions
PeyrSharp.UiHelpers
Links Documentation
GitHub
GitHub Packages</description></item><item><title>Devyus is introducing XValid</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-xvalid/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 11:37:55 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-xvalid/</guid><description>🎉 XValid - First Release 🎉 We are thrilled to announce the first release of XValid - a simple C# validator library that makes it easy to validate various types of data. Whether you need to validate email addresses, ISBNs, IBANs, credit card numbers, IP addresses, or geographic coordinates, XValid has got you covered!
What is XValid? XValid is a lightweight and versatile library designed to help developers implement data validation effortlessly.</description></item><item><title>Peyronnet Group's Subsidiary, Léo Corporation, Sets New Records with a Productive July</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/productive-month-leo-corporation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 16:29:49 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/productive-month-leo-corporation/</guid><description>Léo Corporation, a subsidiary of Peyronnet Group, has had an exceptionally productive month in July, with a flurry of new product launches and updates that have left customers delighted and impressed. The company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to innovation and delivering user-friendly solutions is evident in the array of tools and utilities it introduced to the market. Let&amp;rsquo;s take a closer look at the exciting products and updates that have been rolled out:</description></item><item><title>Safely Downloading Peyronnet Group Apps and Software: Trusted Sources and Misconceptions</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/software-distribution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/software-distribution/</guid><description>Introduction Peyronnet Group is dedicated to delivering high-quality web apps and Windows applications to its users. As a responsible software provider, the company takes utmost care to ensure the safety and security of its products during distribution. In this article, we will explore the trusted sources from which you can safely download Peyronnet Group (including Léo Corporation and Devyus) apps and address some common misconceptions surrounding the safety of their software.</description></item><item><title>The Surging Success of Léo Corporation's Apps and Devyus products: June 2023 Download Evolution</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-june-2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 10:39:20 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-june-2023/</guid><description>Introduction In the dynamic world of software development, companies strive to create innovative solutions that meet the evolving needs of users and developers alike. Two prominent entities making waves in this realm are Léo Corporation and Devyus, both subsidiaries of the Peyronnet Group. Léo Corporation is renowned for its user-friendly and feature-rich apps, while Devyus specializes in providing cutting-edge NuGet packages for developers. As we delve into the data for June 2023, it becomes clear that both Léo Corporation and Devyus have experienced impressive growth in terms of downloads, showcasing their commitment to excellence and the value they bring to their respective industries.</description></item><item><title>PeyrSharp: Version 1.7.0.2307 is now available</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-1702307/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-1702307/</guid><description>Version 1.7.0.2307 of PeyrSharp is now available, let&amp;rsquo;s see what&amp;rsquo;s new.
Changelog PeyrSharp.Core New Added Range() method in Stats (#117) Added Variance() method in Stats (#118) Added StandardDeviation() method in Stats (#119) Updated Improved exceptions PeyrSharp.Env New Added UwpApp record (#120) Added the possibility to get UWP apps asynchronously (#120) NuGet Packages PeyrSharp
PeyrSharp.Core
PeyrSharp.Enums
PeyrSharp.Env
PeyrSharp.Exceptions
PeyrSharp.Extensions
PeyrSharp.UiHelpers
Links Documentation
GitHub
GitHub Packages</description></item><item><title>PeyrSharp: Version 1.6.0.2305 is now available</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-1602305/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 10:44:43 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/peyrsharp-version-1602305/</guid><description>Version 1.6.0.2305 of PeyrSharp is now available, let&amp;rsquo;s see what&amp;rsquo;s new.
Changelog PeyrSharp.Core New Added a method to convert bits to bytes (#100) Added a method to convert bytes to bits (#101) Added a method to convert mach to km/h (#102) Added a method to convert mach to miles/h (#103) Added a StatusInfo class (#104) Added a method that gets the status info of a URL (#105) NuGet Packages PeyrSharp
PeyrSharp.</description></item><item><title>Introducing The Peyronnet Group</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-peyronnet-group/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 09:18:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/introducing-peyronnet-group/</guid><description>Hello everyone, we are the Peyronnet Group - a newly formed organization that brings together two innovative companies in the tech industry: Léo Corporation and Devyus. We are excited to introduce ourselves to you and share our vision for the future.
Léo Corporation, founded in 2017 by Léo Peyronnet, specializes in developing mobile applications and software solutions. Our focus is on creating innovative and user-friendly applications that make life easier and more enjoyable for our users.</description></item><item><title>Léo Corporation and Devyus See Impressive Growth in April 2023.</title><link>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-april-2023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 09:18:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.peyronnet.group/blog/stat-report-april-2023/</guid><description>Introduction In the world of software development, it&amp;rsquo;s not easy to stand out from the crowd. However, Peyronnet Group&amp;rsquo;s subsidiaries, Léo Corporation and Devyus, have managed to do just that. In April 2023, both companies saw impressive growth in their respective areas of expertise.
Léo Corporation First, let&amp;rsquo;s take a closer look at Léo Corporation. This innovative company is known for developing cutting-edge software applications that help users in various areas of their lives.</description></item></channel></rss>